Razu Sardar Masud

UI/UX Designer masudsardar313@gmail.com







SKILLS

User Research

User Interface Design

Wireframe Design

Design System

Compititor Analysis

Prototype

MY DESIGN PROCESS

Discover

Define

Market Analysis

Ideate

Design

Tools I used

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe illustrator

Figjam

Soft Skill

Team-Work

Communications with others tech team

Collaborating in Teams

Management Skills

Empathizing

My Live work

- 1. VISAThing
- 2. <u>Uniclient technologies</u>
- 3. Views bd

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have 02 years of experience as a UX/UI designer specializing in website, mobile app & web-app related digital product design. I work at Visathing Ltd. a Visa processing support center in Bangladesh I oversee strategy, information architecture, and UX design for websites, including wireframes, sitemaps, and prototypes. I can collaborate with overseas project teams to develop intuitive design frameworks.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Visathing Ltd.

March 2023 - Present

Visathing Ltd is a Visa Processing Support Center in Bangladesh. My responsibilities on there is-

- 1. Designing Visathing website
- 2. Design their marketing team website called Uniclients
- 3. Design system Implement
- 4. Design their clients applications UI

Live project Url:

- 1. VISAThing
- 2. Uniclient technologies
- 3. Views bd

BD Calling Ltd.

February 2023 - Febuary 2023

BD Calling Ltd. is a large Design agency in Bangladesh. I worked on there by a supervised of a Senior UX Designer. I assisted on design. Working adhoc stuff a lot.

- 1. Website Design
- 2. Mobile App Design

Health Bondhu Ltd.

February 2022- November 2022

Health Bondhu is a startup teli medicine platfrom. I do design their entire mobile application. Maintain their design systems, prototype the full MVP application

- 1. Mobile app UI Design
- 2. Website Design
- 3. Prototype 130 screen app UI

Course and Certification

<u>Ostad</u>

February 2022- August 2022

I enrolled Ostad 120 Days UX/UI Design bootcamp. Its a fantastic experience for me. On this course we mostly focus on problem solving in Design. I get all of my confusion from them and research on a unique project idea.

UY Lab

November, 2021 - January, 2022

I finished my Graphics and User Interface Design course from UY lab. It was a three-month SEIP project. Here, I learned about graphics design systems, rules, and most importantly human behavior in design. I also understood what international marketplaces require and Color system. It was a great experience

Education

South East University

Summer 2020- Summer 2023

I completed a four-year diploma in engineering and started an undergraduate study in Electrical and Electronics Engineering at Southeast University. Complete My Bsc in 2023 December.